dticloud.com 2011-10-04

# DTI Privacy Policy

Digital Technology International (DTI) is committed to maintaining the privacy of the information you share with us. We will not sell, distribute, or rent information that you provide us through our web site. We will only use the information you share with us for the purposes of enhancing your experience at our web site, or at your request, to send you additional information about our solutions.

The information we collect  
In certain areas of our web site, we may offer to send you additional information or invite you to be included on our mailing list. To process your request, we require that you supply us with your correct contact information and e-mail and/or mailing address for delivery. The transfer of the information is secure and cannot be intercepted by others.

When you submit a support request through the DTI Online Support Center, we ask for any necessary information we need from you to appropriately respond to your inquiry, including your name and e-mail address.

How we use the information we collect.  
Online Information Requests  
We use the personal information you supply to fulfill your request for additional information. Your e-mail address may be used to deliver your requested information, or to confirm that information has been mailed to the street address you provided.  
 **  
Technical Support**  
We use the personal information you supply when you submit a support request to respond to your question. Your e-mail address is used by our Support team to rpocess and communicate the status of your support request.

Surveys and Contests  
Occasionally, DTI requests information through surveys or contents. Requested information may include contact information (such as your name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as your zip code/post code and occupation). Contact information will be used to notify contest winners and award prizes only, unless you indicate that you would like to receive future information (e-mails, special offers, etc.) from DTI. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary, and is limited to those 18 years or olders.

How to gain access to the information we have on file for you  
If you wish to gain access to the information we have on file for you, please send us an e-mail at info@dtint.com.

 **Use of cookies**  
A "cookie" is a small data file stored by your web browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow us to recognize who you are when you arrive at our site by associating the identification numbers in the cookie with other information you have provided. We use cookies on our web site so that you can bypass the initial web page that gives you the option of selecting the Web site for the Public Broadcasting Service (PBS.org). A cookie is stored on your computer when you check the box on this page request that, in future visits to our web site, you are sent directly to the Digital Technology International (DTInt.com) home page.

Notification of changes  
In the future, if there is a change to our Privacy Policy that affects your personally identifiable information, we will notify you by e-mail of the relevant changes.
